漫威出品
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     杏仁斯嘉丽
校对     奶卫联盟
时间轴     今
后期     拳拳和马律师的8T
总监     奶卫联盟
人人影视Pro
人人影视官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存，百度云
app.YYeTs.com
官方网站下载 : 人人影视Pro
最新海外影视剧下载
人人影视Pro
人人官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存
各单位请注意  有警官受伤
All units, we got a 10-66.
需要立即支援
Requesting backup immediately.
-打不开门  -看见什么拿什么
- I can't open my door! - Take what you can.
你们这帮孩子干什么呢
What the hell do you kids think you're doing?
该死  别想从我店里偷东西
Shit! You're not gonna steal from my store!
-快拿走  -我们真的很抱歉
- Just take the stuff! - Hey, hey, we're really sorry.
太迟了
Too late for that.
好吧  好吧  我们放回去
Okay! Okay! We'll put it back.
快  这边  快跑
Hurry, this way! Come on. Run!
敢从我眼皮下逃走
Don't you run from me...
抢劫的王八蛋
...you looter sons of bitches!
他们往那边跑了  拿另一支枪
There they go! Get the other gun!
伙计们  快  他们来了
Guys, hurry! They're coming!
快  这边  快点
Hurry, this way! Come on!
求你停下  我们把东西留下
Please, stop. We'll leave--
糟了
Oh, shit!
跑
Run!
快跑  你个混蛋
Come on, you pieces of shit!
你也想挨枪子
You want some, too?
别  他们还是孩子
Don't do it. They're just kids.
你是谁
Who are you?
捍卫者联盟
第一季  第二集
杰西  是我
Hey, Jess. It's me calling you
给你打了三四通还是19通电话了
for the third or fourth or 19th time.
我听说你家附近受灾惨重
I hear your neighborhood was hit pretty hard,
给我打个电话  让我知道你没事
so call me so I know you're okay.
借过  借过
Excuse me! Excuse me.
真抱歉  我上班迟到了
I'm so sorry. I'm running late for work.
-我挤过去行吗  -你试试吧
- Can I sneak through? - You can try.
谢谢
Thank you.
天啊
Holy shit.
崔西  发生这种事真是太可怕了
Trish, it's really scary when something like this happens.
我怎么跟我孩子说
What do I tell my kids?
我们遭遇了那么多
After everything we've been through,
我们只能认为这是一场事故或者恐怖袭击
we can't help but think it's the incident or terrorism.
是啊  没什么可担心的
True, but there's nothing to worry about.
市长办公室今早证实
The mayor's office confirmed this morning,
是4.6级地震
it was a 4.6 magnitude earthquake.
浅源地震  震中位于地狱厨房
A shallow one, actually, centered in Hell's Kitchen.
据称  地震学家正在检查哈德逊河断层线
I'm told seismologists are looking at a fault line on the Hudson
判断这场地震是否是由它引起的
to see if it could be the source of the problem.
布鲁克林的简  这里是《崔西说》
Jane from Brooklyn, you're on Trish Talk.
你昨晚有什么感觉
What did you feel last night?
肯定不是地震
Not an earthquake, that's for sure.
是啊  布鲁克林不在影响范围之内
Right. Brooklyn's outside the affected area.
不  我是说  不管它是什么  你说得不对
No. I mean, whatever it was, you're reporting it wrong.
听着  我知道人很容易屈服于恐惧  但是
Look, I know it's easy to give into fear, but--
我不是阴谋论者  我是地理学家
I'm no conspiracy theorist. I'm a geologist.
浅源地震可深达80千米
Shallow earthquakes can be up to 50-miles deep.
但昨晚发生的事距地面只有90多米
But whatever happened last night was only 300-feet deep--
等等  什么
Wait, what?
喂
Hello?
好吧  似乎电话线也受到影响了
Okay, so it looks like phone lines may have been affected, too.
但我们继续谈  我想知道各位观众在想什么
But let's keep the conversation going. I want your thoughts next.
《崔西说》  别走开  感谢收听
Trish Talk, stay tuned. Thanks for listening.
到底怎么了
What the hell happened?
和学校负责人的采访
The interview with the school superintendent,
老大说现在就要播
boss says it's going on now.
-你掐了我的通话  -楼上打来电话
- Did you cut off my call? - They called from upstairs.
说我们得先别提地震的事
Said we gotta lay off the earthquake stuff.
我不知道为什么  但听他们的语气
I don't know why, but from the tone they used,
他们很严肃
it was not a conversation.
奈特警探  来得够慢的
Detective Knight. Took long enough to get here.
我已经尽快赶来了  警监
Got here fast as I could, Captain.
房钱是用现金付的  楼下没有记录
Well, the room was paid for in cash. No records downstairs.
这种地方的企业格言都是"一句都不问"
Place like this, company motto is "No questions asked."
我们前脚到  联调局后脚就来了
The FBI showed up just after we did.
国土安全部也快到了
And Homeland Security's on the way.
不管这是什么事
So whatever this is,
我们得到命令  不让媒体报道
we got orders to keep it away from the press.
什么事  发现了一具尸体吗
What is this? We got a body?
比那糟糕  你好像说对了
Worse. Looks like you were right.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
我告诉过你  这些混蛋在运炸药
I told you these assholes were transporting explosives.
确定是他们吗
We sure it's them?
我觉得至少跟他们有关
Uh, at the very least, I think it's connected.
也许炸药是他们的
Maybe the fireworks are theirs,
也许有人从他们那儿偷了炸药
and maybe somebody stole them from 'em.
我加班时间到了  留给你调查清楚
I just sign the overtime. This shit's for you to figure out.
-谁报的警  -这才是有趣之处
- Well, who called this in? - Oh, now that's where it gets funny.
杰西卡·琼斯
Jessica Jones.
我听说过她  我还以为她是个大块头呢
I heard about her. Thought she'd be bigger.
她说她在跟踪一个客户
Says she was following a client.
她肯定被吓坏了
I bet this scared the shit out of her.
传言说  她什么也不怕
Rumor is, she ain't scared of much.
那是她没遇见你
Well, she ain't met you.
你开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
那个租下这间屋子的人
So the guy who rented this room--
我已经说了  我没见过他
I already told you, I didn't see him.
我来之前他就走了
He was gone before I got here.
我已经被困在这四个小时了
Now I have been here four hours.
我能走了吗  笨蛋
Can I go now, dipshit?
等我们完事了你再走
You're done when we're done.
你爱说脏字
You got a mouth.
你注意到了
You noticed.
琼斯女士  你可以走了
Ms. Jones, you can go for now.
愚蠢的混蛋
Stupid son of a bitch.
能相信这个妞吗
Can you believe this chick?
她是不是拿了
Did she just take...
好像没事了
Looks like we're good.
我没发现什么损坏
I don't see any damage.
谢天谢地  没人告诉我
And thank God. No one told me
在纽约还需要买地震保险
I'd need earthquake insurance in New York.
丹尼
Danny?
Danny...
外面还好吗
Everything okay out there?
他们说震中在地狱厨房
They're saying the epicenter was in Hell's Kitchen.
还好你在冥想  你需要休息一下
I'm glad you're meditating. You need a break.
不是休息  是重新集中注意力
It's not a break. I'm refocusing.
要是再遇上那个战士  我会准备好的
If I ever come across that warrior again, I'll be prepared.
好  听着
Yeah. Okay, look.
我一直在想那个死在下水道里的人
I've been thinking about the man who died in the sewer.
他叫你铁拳  他知道些什么
He called you Iron Fist. He knew something.
他不只是个遇害者  我
He wasn't just a victim. I...
我觉得他是我们下一条线索
I think he's our next lead.
他是因反抗手和会而死  对吧
Well, he died fighting the Hand, right?
-那肯定代表了什么  -什么
- That must be a sign. - Of what?
我们有盟友
That we have allies.
我们不是孤军奋战
We're not alone in this.
不
No.
这是我的责任  是我的战斗
This is my responsibility. It's my fight.
是啊  你一直这么说
Yeah. You keep saying that,
但不管他是谁  他受过训练
but whoever he was, he was trained.
他也愿意牺牲
And he was also willing to die.
如果我没从昆仑擅离职守  他可能就不会死了
He might not have died if I hadn't left my post in K'un-Lun.
-我知道你很愤怒  -这不是愤怒的问题
- I know that you are angry-- - This isn't about anger.
是过错
It's about fault.
我只是想说  你不是唯一一个
All I'm saying is you're not the only person
被手和会伤害的人
the Hand has ever hurt.
这也是他的战斗
It was his fight, too.
也是我的
And mine.
你不是孤军奋战
You're not alone in this.
那又怎样
So what?
我们去组个队吗
We just go and find a team to join?
组成军队
An army?
他派我们回纽约  也许那里有我们要找的人
He sent us back to New York. Maybe there are people here.
冒险一搏吧  但我觉得这个险值得冒
It's a shot in the dark, but I think it's one worth taking.
好吧
Okay.
你是想好计划了吗
So I guess you have a plan?
其实
As a matter of fact...
他的武器  他战斗的那把刀
His weapon, the sword he fought with...
不是标准的武士刀  是冢本刀
It wasn't a standard katana. It was a Tsukamoto.
世界上可能只有十把
There are maybe ten of these in the world.
纽约有一家铸刀坊  是世界上最好的之一
There is a workshop here in New York. One of the world's best.
要是死在柬埔寨那个人在这买过东西的话
If the guy who died in Cambodia ever had business here,
可能就是在那家
maybe it was at that workshop.
要是他没买过呢
And what if he didn't?
那我们继续查
Then we keep looking.
如果是陷阱怎么办
What if it's a trap?
那我们就杀出一条血路
Then we fight our way out of it.
丹尼  怎么了
Danny, what?
你和我  我们
You and I, we...
我们之前相信的人都不是善类
We haven't had the greatest luck trusting other people.
是啊
Yeah...
但你相信我吗
but do you trust me?
当然
Of course.
该死  该死
God damn it. God damn it.
福吉  福吉
Foggy. Foggy.
福吉  福
Foggy. Fog--
福吉
Hey, Foggy.
保持清洁
Just keep it clean.
这里没多少人有保险
Not a lot of people have insurance here.
是吗  至少没人死
Yeah? At least nobody died.
多亏了你
Thanks to you.
多数人出狱之后
You know, most people get out of jail and they, uh...
会开瓶啤酒
pop a beer.
我也去买杯酒好了
Maybe I will go get a drink.
我想今晚要不要去艾尔摩酒吧
I was thinking about going by Elmore's tonight.
-艾尔摩酒吧  -对  道格拉斯街上那家
- Elmore's? - Yeah, the bar on Douglass.
我知道这家
Oh, I know it.
在某一群体中颇为著名
Has a reputation for a certain kind of crowd.
我就想这样
That's kinda what I was hoping.
你在抓犯人吗
Are you hunting criminals?
因为你不是说过
'Cause I thought you said you were gonna
要休息一阵子吗
take it easy on that for a while.
有人雇了哈莱姆区的年轻人替他们干脏活
Look, someone's hiring young men in Harlem to do their dirty work.
米丝蒂说纽约警局不知道这些人在干什么
Misty said the NYPD doesn't know what these young men are doing,
但尸体数量在增多  所以
but the body count's growing, so...
好吧
Okay.
纽约警局付你钱让你越俎代庖吗
Is the NYPD gonna pay you for doing their job?
不  但这件事
No. But this...
这个孩子太害怕了  不敢求助
This one kid, he's too afraid to ask for help.
我要介入  免得再有人受伤
I gotta step in before anyone else gets hurt.
-老爹会想让我这么做的  -我知道
- It's... it's what Pop would've wanted. - I know.
你也说过
It's like you said,
要是我们不担负起
if we don't take responsibility
这里的责任  就没人会了
for our neighborhood, no one else will.
你要是想四处打听答案的话
If you're gonna rattle heads for answers,
你应该知道  现在没人去艾尔摩酒吧了
you should know no one goes to Elmore's anymore.
我在庇护所给很多人缝过刀伤  所以知道
I've stitched up enough knife wounds at the shelter to know
如果你要找当今的罪犯聚集地
if you're looking for the current criminal hotspot,
你应该去188街上的一家店
the place to go is on 188th Street.
那个老鼠洞叫麻烦和一对骰子
Rathole called Trouble and a Pair of Dice.
他们说  你给爱乐乐团
I'm told your donation to
捐的钱刚好能支付重新装修
the Philharmonic should just about cover the remodeling.
用小钱换取更大的利益
A small price to pay in the larger scheme of things.
因为你大力支持我们
You know, with the kind of support you've provided,
我们希望下一场晚会能请到你
we would love to host you at our next gala.
我一直都更喜欢私密一些的环境
I've always preferred a more intimate setting.
当然了
Of course.
你要求的那首曲子很有趣
The piece you've requested is a curious one.
勃拉姆斯C小调的作品很少
Brahms didn't often write in C minor.
其实  贝多芬钟爱C小调
Matter of fact, that was Beethoven's key of choice.
但在这  贝多芬的影响很明显
But here, Beethoven's influence is quite pronounced.
这不是影响  这是直接回应
It's not influence. It was a direct response.
勃拉姆斯只是想证明他也能写C小调
All Brahms wanted was to prove that he could do it, too.
他就这么小气
He was petty like that.
你对音乐史的见识之广  总是让我惊叹
Your insight on music history, it never ceases to amaze me.
不算什么  只是偶然间学到的知识
Oh, it's nothing. It's just stuff I picked up along the way.
失陪一下
If you'll excuse me.
好
Of course.
-遇到麻烦了  -什么麻烦
- There's been a complication. - What kind?
有一堵墙挡住了入口  上面写满了碑文
There's a wall blocking our access. It is full of inscriptions.
都是关于昆仑的  似曾相识
Familiar phrases about K'un-Lun.
-拆掉  -我们试过了  都不行
- Tear it down. - We've tried. Nothing works.
我们之前从来没碰到过墙
We've never encountered a wall before.
他们知道我们终有一天会到这
They knew we'd get here... eventually.
也许我们应该重新考虑计划
Perhaps we should rethink our plan.
你我之间的差别就在这
That's always been the difference between us.
你很容易重新考虑  我比较固执
You are quick to rethink. I'm a bit more stubborn.
要是他们想让我们永远都碰不到
If they wanted to take this one from us forever,
他们会毁掉它  而不是保护它
they would've destroyed it, not protected it.
-也就是说那不是一堵墙  -我亲眼见过
- Which means it's not a wall. - I've seen it.
是一扇门
It's a door.
它注定会被打开
It's meant to be opened.
用什么打开
By what?
昆仑的长老始终有坚定的信念
The conviction of the elders of K'un-Lun was always unwavering.
他们觉得这是美德
They think it's a virtue.
但最后  只会让他们变得容易被人看透
But in the end, all it ever did was make them predictable.
他们把它锁起来了
They've locked it away.
但没有钥匙的锁不叫锁
But a lock is not a lock without a key.
从一开始
And from the beginning,
他们就把一样东西看得比其他都重要
they have valued one thing above all else.
双橡树运输公司
无记录
记名提货单
双橡木运输公司
资产转移
舍温集团和双橡树运输公司
乌腾特公司和社文集团
什么
What?
开玩笑吧
You've gotta be kidding me.
You've got to be kidding me.
-我有问题  -什么
- Hi. I'm confused. - Okay?
我在调查这家公司
I'm looking into this company,
但他们把资产
but they've been transferring assets
从一家公司转移到另一家
from one corporation to the next.
就好像一直在改名字  空壳公司之类的
Like, they're changing their name, shell company stuff.
但我还是不知道他们究竟是干什么的
Yet, I have no idea what it is they actually do.
你想让我做什么
Oh, so what do you need from me?
最古老的记录能追溯到1820年
The oldest record dates back to 1820,
听起来很疯狂  但我还要再往前查
but as crazy as this sounds, I need to go back further than that.
那你得去市中心的历史资料分部
Oh, well, you... you wanna go to the historical branch uptown.
而且需要预约
And you'll need an appointment.
谢谢
Okay, thanks.
其实不需要
Actually, you don't.
杰西卡  我们得谈谈
Jessica, we need to talk.
霍加斯
Hogarth.
好久不见  乔茜
Been a long time, Josie.
我真是想死这个地方了
I can't tell you how much I miss this place.
城里人先生竟然想我们这个小破店
Oh, so Mr. Uptown misses our humble establishment.
工作怎么样
How's work?
和解的事我听说了
I heard about that settlement.
-一千一百万  -是啊
- Eleven million. - Yeah.
你确定一分钱不要吗
You sure you want to stay pro bono?
能帮上忙我就很开心了
I'm just happy I could help.
谢谢  乔茜
Thanks, Josie.
你呢  近来如何
How about you? How's things?
挺好的  大办公室
Good. Big office.
跟我们小时候梦想的完全不同
Far from what we dreamed about doing when we were kids,
但至少我能经常见到玛茜
but at least I get to see Marci a lot.
-下班以后  -真好  福吉
- After hours. - That's great, Foggy.
我是说坦诚相见
Naked, I mean.
感谢你联系我  好久没见了
Hey, thanks for reaching out. It's, uh... been a while, huh?
没错
That it has.
我跟凯伦聊过  她说你们喝咖啡去了
I talked to Karen. She said you guys grabbed coffee.
我不想打探  但你们到哪一步了
I don't mean to pry, but where you guys at?
情感状态
Relationship status?
-我们在"弄清楚两个人之间的关系"  -好
- We are "Figuring ourselves out." - Good.
你告诉她你的小秘密之后
After you told her your little secret,
幸运的是她没吓得取消我们的律师资格
lucky she didn't freak out and have us both disbarred.
-我们可以相信她的  -我知道
- We can trust her. - I know.
你也可以相信我
You can trust me, too.
昨晚之后你感觉如何
How you doing after last night?
还好  昨晚真疯狂
Uh, yeah, good. It was, uh, crazy.
我说的不是这个
That's not what I'm talking about.
你不用说出来  你的指关节说明了一切
You don't have to say it. Your knuckles speak volumes.
你打电话就是为了这个  看我做没做傻事
That why you called? To see if I'd done anything stupid?
我没说是傻事  我知道你在努力
Nobody's saying it's stupid. I know you're trying.
地震了  福吉  警察没来
Earth shook, Foggy. The cops weren't coming.
马特  别这样
Matt, stop!
不管你在经历什么  我都不多说什么
Whatever you're going through, I'm not gonna judge.
但我真心觉得我能帮你一把
But I do think I can help you through it.
我是来给你一些东西的
I came to offer you something.
这些卷宗我现在忙得没时间处理
These are case files. Stuff I'm too busy to handle right now.
从毫无价值的案子到能改变人一生的重要案子
Ranging from petty bullshit to life-changingly important.
拜托  我用不着你施舍
Come on, I don't need your charity.
不是施舍  这是外包
This isn't that. It's outsourcing.
最重要的是  反正你也在干这种活
Most importantly, it's the type of stuff you're doing anyway.
渎职  工人的赔偿金  需要伸张正义的好人
Malpractice. Workmen's comp. Good people who need justice.
要是你接下这些  它会让你忙得团团转
If you take these, it'll keep you up-to-your-eyeballs busy.
下次你就会对在夜里行侠仗义
And the next time you're on the fence
持中立态度了
about stepping out at night...
因为你忙着当另外一种英雄
you'll be too busy being another kind of hero.
这不是条出路  不是长久之计
It's not a solution. Not long-term.
但眼下
But right now...
我能想到的最好的就这样了
it's the best I got.
要是行不通怎么办
What if it doesn't work?
那我们至少也试过了
Then we tried anyway.
好吧  谢谢  哥们
All right. Thanks, man.
-你在这干什么  -跟你说话
- What are you doing here? - Talking to you.
这座城市有九百万人
In a city of nine million people,
我们就这么巧遇上了
we just happen to bump into each other?
你跟踪我吗
Are you having me followed?
真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
你没回我电话
You haven't returned my calls.
谁的电话我都没回
I haven't returned anybody's calls.
我自然认为你是针对我
I couldn't help but take it personally.
也许你就该这么想
Maybe you should.
我是来让你小心点
I'm here to ask you to be careful.
-小心什么  -联调局  国土安全部
- Be careful why? - FBI, Homeland Security.
不管你昨晚碰上的是什么  肯定是件大事
Whatever it is you stumbled onto last night, it's big.
我没碰上什么  我有意接了一个案子
I didn't stumble onto anything. I took a case on purpose.
-我听说你拒绝了  -你听错了
- Oh, I... I heard you'd put that off. - You heard wrong.
我们够熟了
Listen, I... I know you well enough,
所以我就直说了
so I'm going to say this very simply.
别管了
Walk away.
不管这是什么事  让联调局处理吧
Whatever this is, let the feds handle it.
在你昨晚取得重大发现之后
After your rather explosive discovery last night,
你客户的丈夫就上了联邦监视名单
your client's husband has been placed on a federal watch list.
现在成了国家安全的问题了
It's now a matter of national security.
也就是说有上百名警官
Which means hundreds of law enforcement officers.
齐心协力  虎视眈眈
All hands on deck. Every ego on display.
只要出现一个过分热心的想要拯救世界的探员
All it takes is one overzealous agent who wants to save the world,
这个约翰·雷蒙德
and this man, John Raymond,
还有任何涉嫌协助他的人都会被当即射杀
and anyone suspected of aiding him will be shot on sight.
这个人的资料中
There is nothing in this guy's profile
没有一处表明他是恐怖分子
that suggests he's a terrorist.
他们刚刚在那家汽车旅馆搜出了
They just found enough C-4
能夷平整个街区的C4炸药
in that motel room to level a city block.
你觉得是什么情况
What do you think it looks like?
政府不抓到他是不会罢休的
The government is not going to rest until they've got him.
我不想看你冒着枪林弹雨
I just... I don't wanna see you caught in the cross fire.
是为了保护我还是保护你自己
Is this about protecting me or protecting you?
放一天假  喝一杯或多喝几杯  这是你应得的
Take the day off. Have a drink or five. You've earned it.
要不是因为你  他们找不到那些炸药
They wouldn't have found those explosives if it weren't for you.
你今天救了好多人的命
You actually saved lives today.
省省吧  霍加斯  别担心我
Well, save yourself some time, Hogarth. Stop worrying about me.
鸡尾酒酒吧
这只是看起来像塑料
This only looks like plastic,
但它是纯金的
but I'm telling you it's solid gold.
地震让所有人都疯了
Earthquake has everyone going crazy.
没人会注意到小东西
Nobody's paying attention to the little things,
比如钱包里缺了什么东西
like what is or isn't in their wallets.
-欢迎回来  大块头  -我们得谈谈
- Welcome back, big man. - We need to talk.
-你就这么谈  -我要答案  特科
- This is how you talk? - I want answers, Turk.
至于怎么得到就看你了
How I get 'em is up to you.
凯奇  这破事哪里跟我有关了
Cage, what part of this shit looks like it's up to me?
玛莉娅和沙兹  我需要知道他们想干什么
Mariah and Shades... I need to know what they're up to.
据我所知  什么也不想
Far as I know, nothing.
你走之后他们也不见了
They ghosted right after you left.
就算他们在做什么  也是我不知道的事
If they got their hands in anything, it ain't stuff I've seen.
那是谁在招募哈莱姆区的孩子  害他们被杀
Then who's recruiting kids out of Harlem and getting them killed?
孩子  哥们  我看起来像家长教师会的吗
Kids? Man, do I look like the PTA?
深夜出动  报酬高  结局惨
Late-night work. Pays well, ends bad.
没人知道他们在干什么
No one seems to know what they're doing.
我想帮忙  但我什么也不知道
Look, I'd love to help, but I don't know shit.
我觉得你知道
I think you do.
好吧  我是听说过
Okay! I heard about it!
但没人来问我  明白吗
But ain't nobody come asking me, okay?
我是个老派的人  不掺和这种事
I'm too old-school for this anyway.
他们在干什么  谁让他们做的
What are they doing? And who are they doing it for?
有个新来的  他很显眼
Some new guy. Can't miss him.
我不知道他叫什么
I don't know his name.
大家都叫他白帽子
Everyone just calls him White Hat
因为他对时尚见解独特
on account of his unique fashion sense.
也是百分之百的黑人
Real deal African brother, too, man.
白色西服  巴拿马帽  鳄鱼皮鞋
White suit, Panama hat, alligator shoes.
-我去哪找他  -我只见过他几次
- Where can I find him? - I've only seen him a couple times.
试试去151街和阿姆斯特丹
Try around 151st and Amsterdam.
要是你没说实话  我会回来的
If this isn't the truth, I'll be back.
那时候你可不会太喜欢我
And you won't like me then.
我现在就不喜欢你
I don't like you now.
有人吗
Hello?
我竟然想住在这
Is it weird that I wanna live here?
丹尼
Danny.
丹尼  这就是冢本刀
Danny, this is a Tsukamoto.
就像你给我看过的那把
Just like the one you showed me.
是啊
Yeah.
但一般不会开刃
But you don't sharpen these.
除非你想用它们
Unless you plan on using them.
丹尼
Danny...
天啊
Oh, my God.
他没死多久
It hasn't been long.
还有体温
He's still warm.
有人被拖走了
Someone was dragged out of here.
肯定是手和会干的
This must have been the Hand.
那这些是什么人
Then who are these people?
我不知道
I don't know.
丹尼
Danny?
怎么了
What is it?
是昆仑
It's K'un-Lun.
米丝蒂  我是卢克
Misty, it's Luke.
我有所发现
I think I found something.
你应该弄张逮捕令  过来找我
You should get a warrant and get down here.
-我要逮捕谁吗  -应该吧  涉及到孩子
- Am I making arrests? - Think so. It's about those kids.
我也许找到线索了
I may have found a lead.
卢克  你在哪  给我个地址
Luke? Where are you? I need an address.
-算了  -什么
- Never mind. - What?
-我得先解决掉一个人  -不行  卢克
- I gotta take care of someone first. - No. Luke--
把预约推后十分钟  富兰克林  我要说句话
Push my calls ten minutes. Franklin, I need a word.
待会见
See you later.
你还有多少案子  我要你盯着点东西
How's your case load? I need you to keep an eye on something.
-很乐意  -但要私下进行
- Happy to. - But it's gotta be off the record.
好
Okay.
之前有个在这工作的自由职业者
Someone who used to work here, a freelancer...
她可能会失控  她叫杰西卡·琼斯
She has a tendency to go rogue. Her name is Jessica Jones.
你我这次谈话从来没发生过
Now you and I never had this conversation,
但只要她一陷入麻烦
but the second she gets herself into trouble,
当务之急就是让我们离麻烦越远越好
priority one is keeping that trouble very far away from us.
好
Okay.
抱歉  让我把话说明白
So... Sorry, uh, just to be clear...
这只是以防万一吧  她现在没什么麻烦吧
this is all just in case? She's not in trouble now?
我倒想  事关杰西卡  只是时间问题
I wish. With Jessica, it's just a matter of time.
杰西  你去哪了
Jess, where have you been?
-抱歉  我今天太累了  -我也是
- Sorry, I had a long day. - Me, too.
演播室有些事情不太对劲
Something weird's going on at the studio.
怎么个奇怪法
Weird how?
地震的事  我觉得
This tremor stuff, I think...
他们想让我掩盖这件事
I think they want me to sweep it under the rug.
崔西  我再打给你
Trish, I gotta call you back.
马尔科姆  你要来我家的话  我怎么跟你说的
Malcolm, what did I tell you about coming in my apartment?
我告诉你别再跟着我了
I told you to stop following me.
这说不通
It doesn't make sense.
为什么这些人有昆仑的图片
Why do these people have a picture of K'un-Lun?
他们还知道什么
And what else did they know?
有人来了
Someone's coming.
你们从那边开始
You guys start over there.
他们想干什么
What are they doing?
我不知道
I don't know.
但他们别想逃脱
But they're not gonna get away with this.
你妻子来找过我
Your wife came to me.
她很担心
She was worried.
-我告诉过你别管  -雷蒙德先生  相信我
- I told you to stay away. - Mr. Raymond, trust me.
现在我真的后悔没听你的话
Right now, I wish I'd listened.
你在跟他们合作吗
Are you working with them?
跟谁
With who?
你知道我说的是谁
You know who I'm talking about.
我单干
I work alone.
一直都是
Always has.
我说过  几乎没人雇我
Look, like I said, I'm barely on the payroll.
好吧  不管你怎么想
Okay, whatever you think is going on...
不管你觉得现在什么状况
whatever you think is happening here--
这里的状况我一清二楚  我知道得太多了
I know damn well what is happening here. I know too much.
接下来  他们就要杀我的家人
And next, they'll come after my family.
他们是谁  谁要杀你
Who's they? Who do you think is after you?
我不能告诉你  我
I can't tell you. I...
我不想这么干  我是个好人
This... this is not me. I'm a good man.
你一定要告诉她
Make sure you tell her that.
好吧  但愿你能亲自告诉她
Okay, with any luck, you're gonna tell her that yourself.
你家人很担心
Now your family is worried.
他们想知道发生了什么
They just wanted to know what happened.
还有警察
And the cops...
他们想知道你为什么囤积炸药
They just wanna know why you started stockpiling explosives.
什么
What?
我无处可去了
There's nowhere to go.
他们会找到我的  他们会伤害我的
They'll find me. They'll... they'll hurt me.
说实话  如果你伤害我的朋友  我就加倍奉还
To be honest, if you hurt my friend, I'm gonna hurt you worse.
我只是想阻止他们
I was just trying to stop them.
-他们会炸掉整座城市的  -谁
- They're gonna take down the city. - Who?
你要是不告诉我他们是谁  我就没法帮你
I can't help you if you won't tell me who.
我就不该到这来
I should never have come here.
天啊  太迟了
Oh, my God. It's too late.
你别想得到
You can't have this.
你没事吧
You okay?
站在那别动
Hold it right there.
-糟了  -转过来
- Shit. - Turn around.
手举起来
Get your hands up!
快
Now!
好啊  混蛋们
Hey there, assholes.
-你们跟手和会是一伙的  -不
- You with the Hand? - No!
-你在那干什么  -不知道  我只是个清洁工
- What are you doing in there? - I don't know! I'm just a cleanup!
-为他们收拾烂摊子  -我不知道他们是谁
- Cleanup for them? - I don't know who they are!
别撒谎
Don't lie to me!
-你是谁  -你是谁
- Who are you? - Who are you?
-你没事吧  -你在干什么
- You all right? - What are you doing?
聊着天呢
In between gigs, huh?
-你还想找打吗  -不
- You back for more? - No.
我们还没动真格呢
We've not even started.
你是什么材料做的
What are you made of?
记住  是你先挑事的
Just remember, you started this.
趴下
Stay down.
不许动
Freeze!
丹尼  我们得走了
Danny! We have to go!
跪下  快
Get on your knees, now!
跪下  手举起来
On your knees! Hands in the air!
你那边除了你都死了
Everyone else on your side is dead.
你知道我是谁  我也知道你是谁
You know who I am, I know who you are,
我们闲话少说
so let's skip the wartime banter.
时间我可浪费不起
Time is not something I can afford to waste.
不是为了你  是为了我  我要把眼罩摘掉
Not for your benefit but for mine, I'm taking the blinds off.
可别咬我  老朋友
Try not to bite, old friend.
那样有失尊严
It's undignified.
亚历山德拉
Alexandra.
棍叟
Stick.
我们要说的可太多了
We have so much to talk about.
-有必要吗  -标准流程而已  不是针对你
- Are these necessary? - Standard protocol. Nothing personal.
约翰·雷蒙德
John Raymond,
我们在你办公室或者家里发现的那具尸体
the body we found in your office slash apartment.
马尔科姆·杜卡斯  你的朋友在大厅尽头受审
Malcolm Ducasse, your friend being interrogated down the hall.
还有杰西卡
And Jessica...
-我不知道这是怎么回事  -琼斯
- Look, I don't know what-- - ...Jones.
真的吗
Really?
你对于我来说一直都是个大麻烦  你知道吗
You have been a huge pain in my ass all day, you know that?
-我会因为什么被起诉吗  -现在还不会
- Am I being charged with something? - Not yet.
但你可能打断了全城范围内的调查
But you might have interrupted a city-wide investigation.
你从我的犯罪现场偷了证据
You stole evidence from my crime scene.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你还害得我的一条线索被杀
And you got my one lead killed.
-我是想帮他  -但你没帮上
- I was trying to help him. - But you didn't.
-他家人很担心  -是吗
- His family was worried. - Yeah?
那现在他们得担心葬礼安排了
Well, now all they have to worry about are funeral arrangements.
你的办公室现在是犯罪现场
Your office is currently a crime scene,
但我需要你配合
but I need your cooperation.
-我是嫌犯吗  -刑事破坏
- Am I a suspect? - Criminal mischief...
毁坏证据  轻微偷盗
tampering with evidence, petty larceny--
-我是谋杀嫌犯吗  -不是
- Am I a murder suspect? - No.
但你应该知道谁杀了他
But I think you know who killed him.
-是啊  他开枪自杀的  -那你在追谁
- Yeah. He shot himself. - Then who were you chasing?
警官  除非你有理由拘留我
Officer, unless you have a reason to hold me--
别跟我扯"警官"那些没用的  你看见什么了
Don't give me that "officer" bullshit. What did you see?
我知道你觉得自己在做本职工作
Look, I know that you think you're just doing your job,
但我告诉你  这个案子不一般
but I'm telling you, this case isn't normal.
你搅进了奇怪的事情里
You are walking into some weird-ass shit.
杰西卡·琼斯  别说了
Jessica Jones, stop talking.
结束了
Hi, this is over.
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
我叫马修·默多克  是你的律师
My name is Matthew Murdock. I'm your attorney.